(English Subtitle) Growing.Pains.S01E08 -= Slice.of.Life =- Subripped by zerox
在巴西内陆某些地区.
You know that in certain remote areas of Brazil...
咖啡被认为是春药
coffees considered to be an aphrodisiac.
再喝点吗？
More coffee?
有请
Please.
看来有效
I think it's working.
这样的话.
Well, in that case....
要喝就喝吧
Well, it's there if you need it.
真喜欢周六的早上，多么的宁静
Oh, I love Saturday mornings. So tranquil.
仔细聆听，人能听到落叶的声音
You know, if you listen carefully, you can almost hear the leaves fall.
好大一块落叶
Big leaves this year.
你这臭蛋!
You scuzzball!
你才是臭蛋!
You're the scuzzball!
-去你妈的! -去你妈的!
- Your mama! - Your mama!
等等，孩子们 你们有着同一个妈妈
Hey, wait, kids, kids, kids. You both have the same mama.
这是怎么了？
Come on, what's this all about?
凯罗把水龙头关掉了
Carol turned the water off!
我来淋浴，她把水龙头关掉了
I was taking a shower, and she turned the water off!
我是迫不得已，他不让我进去
I had to. He wouldn't let me in the bathroom.
我不愿、意
I was indisposed.
他进去1个半小时了
Well, he was in there for an hour and a half.
1小时33分钟22秒
One hour, 33 minutes, and 22 seconds.
他想要破世界纪录
He's trying to get into the World Record Book.
什么记录？人肉泡菜？
As what, Ben? The Human Prune?
不，世上最长的淋浴
No, for taking the longest shower.
纪录只是374小时 我很容易就能打破
The record's only 374 hours. I can beat that, easy.
本，300小时，那是两个星期
Ben, 300, that's two weeks.
不能留在水里那么久
You can't stay in the water that long.
人们也是这样对雅克说的
That's what they told Jacques Cousteau.
本，雅克有一艘潜艇
Ben, Jacques had a submarine.
他九岁时没有吧
Not when he was nine.
本.
Ben....
我想要永垂不朽.
Great. I wanted to be immortal.
结果只是湿漉漉而已
Instead, I'm just wet.
永垂不朽？
Immortal?
什么时候开始这样想的？
How long have you wanted to be immortal?
自从两岁开始
Since I was two.
若你答应我不霸占浴室 我也许能帮你
Well, if you promise to stay out of the bathroom, maybe I'll help you.
好吧
Okay.
不知道最长时间不洗澡的纪录是谁
Hey, I wonder what's the longest anyone's gone without a shower.
那是上个暑假的麦克
I think it was Mike last summer.
刚才谈到宁静的周六早晨
Well, we we're talking about those tranquil Saturday mornings.
看来他也进不了浴室
I guess he couldn't get in the bathroom, either.
爸爸妈妈，我要学空手道
Hey, Mom, Dad, I want to take karate.
我要破板，破砖
I want to split boards. I want to break bricks.
快点去把我们家烟囱藏起来
Quick. Hide the chimney.
爸爸，我是认真的
Come on, Dad, I'm serious.
今天开始第一堂课
And the first class starts today.
麦克，怎么突然热衷于空手道了？
Mike, why are you so hot, all of a sudden, about taking karate?
爸爸？ 妈妈竟然问为什么要学空手道
Can you believe that, Dad? She wants to know why I want to take karate.
-麦克 -什么？
- Mike? - Yeah, Dad?
为什么要学空手道？
Why do you want to take karate?
不知道，我就是想学
I don't know. I just want to.
很好的分析能力
The analytical mind at work.
做每件事情都需要理由的吗？
Come on, Dad. Does everybody have to have a reason for everything they do?
-不是的 -那就对了
- No. - There you go, then.
-那么你会给学费？ -不会
- So you'll pay for the lessons? - No.
-为什么？ -不为什么
- Why not? - No reason.
麦克，我和你爸都想问你.
Mike, I think I speak for both your father and myself when I ask you:
空手道班上有女同学？
Is there a girl in this class?
什么？
What?
女同学？
A girl?
我生气了
You know, I resent that.
那就是“有”吧？
I take that as a "Yes."
你们在说什么？
What are you guys talking about?
记得你那次非得学骑马吗？
Remember when you just had to take horseback-riding lessons?
你说要克服对大型动物的恐惧
Yeah, cause you said it would help you overcome your fear of large animals?
无可否认，黛比真的很巨大
Yeah, well, you gotta admit, Debbie DiZomba was large.
是的，记得你非得要学 苏格兰民间舞蹈吗？
Right. And remember when you just had to learn Scottish folk dancing?
我喜欢学习文化
Hey, I was starved for culture.
爸爸，这次是不同的 空手道是男人的运动
This is different, Dad. This is karate. It's a man's sport.
-而且学费几乎为零 -很好
- And it costs next to nothing. - Oh, good, good.
有1块钱散钱吗？
You got change for $1?
怎么个几乎为零？
Okay, how next to nothing?
只是125块
It's only $125, Dad.
而且还包括了几块训练用的砖头
And that includes a dozen training bricks.
麦克，给你10块钱
Mike, heres $10.
去买个汉堡包，更便宜
Go buy her a burger. It's cheaper.
-给你倒了咖啡 -亲爱的，不能放这
- Brought you some coffee. - Hi, honey. Not there. No, no.
请给我一个垫子
Would you get me a coaster there, please?
我这个星期擦了桌子
I polished this thing within an inch of it's life this week.
现在要保持桌面的温度？
And now you're just keeping it warm?
杰森，你在干什么？ 有何不可告人的东西？
What are you doing, Jason, that you don't want me to see?
-我？ -你在测试什么？
- Me? - Looks like you're working on a test.
可以这样说
I guess you could say that, yeah.
-那是什么测试？ -无聊的测试
- Well, what kind of a test is it? - It's a dull test.
测什么的？
I mean, what's it for?
测试有多无聊
Well, it's a test to measure dullness.
太无聊了，我甚至不欲提起
It's so dull, I can't even talk about it.
杰森？
Jason?
这是婚姻吻合度测试 给我的病人夫妇的
Okay, it's a marriage-compatibility test l"m planning to give a couple of my patients.
真有趣!
How fun!
-测测我们怎么样 -测测我们怎么样
- Let's take it and see how we do. - Let's take it and see how we do.
我知道我们会这么反应
I knew we would say that.
-别这样食古不化 -别这样食古不化
- Don't be such a stick-in-the-mud. - Such a stick-in-the-mud.
我这么容易被看穿？
Am I that predictable?
不是的，不是的
No, no.
你是无拘无束，性格刚烈
No, you're spontaneous and impetuous...
这是我爱你的地方
and that's what I love about you.
-别自作聪明 --别自作聪明
- Don't be a wise guy. - Don't be such a wise guy.
麦姬，这是问题夫妇的测试
Maggie, this is a test for couples having problems.
用来确定冲突的地方
It pinpoints areas of conflict.
我们之间没有冲突
We have no conflict.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
-我要测试，你呢？ -我不要
- I want to take the test. Do you? - No.
瞧？冲突来了
See? Conflict.
麦姬，这测试很无聊
Maggie, it's a boring test.
我看到的则不然
Not from what I see here.
这些问题有深度，巧妙，有哲理
The questions are profound, astute, full of insight.
特别是猥亵的那些
Especially the smutty ones.
是啊，第12题
Yes, Number 12.
喜欢这个的话，看看33题
If you like that, wait till you get to Number 33.
杰森，填一张试试
Oh, come on, Jason. Fill one out.
若是答得好，我给你.
If you do well, I'll give you a big...
37？
37?
还有什么能更满足.
Well, what more incentive...
煽情，冲动又喜欢冒险的丈夫？
could any red-blooded, card-carrying husband ask for?
-对了!
-42 - 42. - Bingo!
邦纳，对，还记得那个空手道小子吗？
Yeah, Boner. Yeah, look, remember when we saw The Karate Kid?
对，那老头对那小子说的.
Yeah. Okay. Well, what did the old man tell the kid...
学空手道的最重要目的是什么？
was the most important reason to study karate?
不在，我出去买花生了
No, no, I was out getting the Goobers.
对
Yeah.
好，等等
Yeah, good. All right, wait.
很好，邦纳，好得很
Good, Boner, good. Yeah, great.
好的，谢谢，再见
Yeah, okay. All right, thanks a lot. Bye-bye.
-爸爸，能聊两句吗？ -可以
- Dad. Hey, can we talk? - Sure.
今天早上你不让我学空手道.
Look, I know that I kind of got upset...
我也许反应过度了
this morning when you said I couldn't take the karate lessons.
也许我以前曾经借上课来结识女孩子
And I know that, in the past, I may have used these activities to meet girls.
但我真的希望你能让我 参加空手道学习班
But I'm really glad you put your foot down about these karate lessons, Dad...
它能让人扪心自问.
because it forced me to look deeper into myself...
“麦克，为什么要学习空手道？”
and ask, "Mike, why do you want to take these lessons? "
我知道答案了
And the answer came to me, Dad.
“学习空手道是因为..”
"Mike, you want to take karate..."
“它能培养纪律性”
"because it develops discipline."
不单肉体上的纪律性 还包括心灵上的纪律性
Not only physical discipline, Dad, but spiritual discipline as well.
这对你来说很重要
That's important to you, is it?
是的
Oh, yeah, Dad.
因为人若没有纪律性.
I mean, hey, with no discipline, each one of us...
“就像在欲望的海洋失去船舵一样”
"is like a rudderless craft in a sea of conflicting desires."
还有.
And you know what, Dad?
我需要空手道给予我的船舵
I need the rudder that karate will give me.
我明白了
I see.
你的意思是.
So what you're saying is that...
学空手道会让你达到.
you're taking karate to help you achieve this spiritual state of...
唐霍的精神境界？
Don Ho?
是的，唐霍
Right. Don Ho.
麦克，唐霍是唱的 夏威夷歌手
Mike, Don Ho is the Hawaiian singer who recorded Tiny Bubbles.
对，非常高尚
Right. Very spiritual guy.
他已经坚持了46分钟! 这次能成功!
He's up to 46 minutes now! We're going to do it!
成功？成功扭伤臀部？
Do what? Throw out his hip?
不，破连续模仿猫王的纪录
No, break the worlds record for the most consecutive hours of imitating Elvis!
这不是模仿，这是折磨
I take it you're going for endurance here, not accuracy.
还需多久才能破纪录？
How much longer before he gets in the book?
-现在几点？ -1点半
- What time is it now? - 1 :30.
需要到周四往后一周
A week from Thursday.
凯罗
Carol.
本!
Ben!
虽然猫王很感动.
I'm sure Elvis would be touched but...
但总不能这样下去12天
you can't keep this up for another 12 days.
本？
Ben?
猫王死了
The King is dead.
对不起
I'm sorry.
怎样了？
How do you feel?
★我非常震惊
I'm all shook up
-测试完成没有？ -完成了
- So, did you finish scoring our tests yet? - Yeah.
-结果如何？ -其中一项是你缺乏耐性
- Well, what's it say? What's it say? - For one thing, it says you're impatient.
杰森，别这样 我们到底合得来吗？
Oh, come on, Jason. Are we compatible or not?
-我合得来，你不行 -去你的
- I am. You're not. - Darn.
你自己看吧，我们的分数很高
No, go ahead. See for yourself. We got an excellent score.
差不多完全吻合
Agreed on just about everything.
特别是猥亵的问题
Especially the smutty questions.
这有一条不吻合
Heres one we disagreed on.
“你的爱好是什么？”
"What is your favorite hobby? "
-杰森.. -怎么了？
- Oh, Jason. - What?
我答“园艺”，你答“收集棒球卡片”
I said "gardening, " and you said "collecting baseball cards."
我们的婚姻出现裂缝了
How can we go on with this rift in our marriage?
无法继续了
It's impossible.
我们得卖掉房子，瓜分孩子
Well have to sell the house and divide the kids.
麦克给你了
You take Mike.
这一题你又答错了
Heres another one you screwed up.
“你睡在床的哪一边？”
"What side of the bed do you sleep on? "
我答“左边”，你答“左边”
I said "the left" and you said "the left."
其实没有错
Well, that's right.
你睡在床的左边，我睡在你的左边
You take up most of the bed, and I sleep on what's left.
又一题答错了
Oh, no, heres another one you botched up.
杰森，答问题要认真点
Jason, you should be more careful.
“你会对配偶有所隐瞒吗？”
"Would you ever keep anything from your spouse? "
我答什么了？
What did I say?
你答“会”
You said "yes."
我就是这个意思
Well, that's what I meant.
什么？
What?
你怎么隐瞒我了？
What do you mean, you'd keep things from me?
那等于你骗我
That's like saying that you'd lie to me.
不，别弯曲我的题目
No, no, you're twisting my answer.
问题是“你会对配有有所隐瞒吗？”
The question simply asks, "Would you ever keep anything from your spouse? "
题目的范围很广呢
"Anything" is a big word.
任何事情都不能隐瞒
It means anything.
谢谢你的解释
Well, thanks for clearing that up.
那么告诉我骗子的意思是什么？
Now will you tell me what "liar" means?
拜托，麦姬，别小题大做
Come on, Maggie, what are you making such a big deal of this for?
我坦诚对你
I've always been honest with you.
是吗？
Oh?
是的
Yes.
还记得有人在你的果汁机上 放泥巴吗？
Remember when somebody tried to mix cement in your blender?
我立刻挺身而出说“是本干的”
I stepped forward right away and said, "Ben did it."
杰森，这一点都不好笑
Jason, you think this is funny, don't you?
亲爱的，我只是说.
No, honey, I'm just saying--
我也记得.
Well, I'll tell you what I remember.
我记得在马塔酒店.
I remember the Mattapoisett Inn.
那是我们蜜月的地方
The.... Yes, where we had our honeymoon.
是的，回想第一个晚上.
Yes, now remember that first night...
我们坐在干柴烈火前.
and remember in front of the fireplace when we sat--
亲爱的，火炉旁的事我都记得
Honey, I remember what we did in front of that fireplace.
你说了些什么？
Remember what you said?
我说过“再来一次”
Yes, I said, "Lets try that again...
“这次不用冰块”
"without the ice cubes."
你还说坦诚是幸福婚姻的关键
You also said that total honesty is essential to a happy marriage.
结婚后我还这样说？
I said that after we we're married?
好吧，我是说过
Okay, okay. I said that.
但我们现在更加成熟了
But we're more mature now.
所以我们就能睁眼说白话
So, now we lie like rugs.
不，只是某些事情不会主动说出来
No, I'm only saying that there are some things that I might not volunteer.
什么事情？给我一个例子
Well, like what things? Give me an example.
例子？
An example?
两列火车，相向而行.
Two trains, traveling from opposite directions--
-杰森 -火车A时速85英里.
- Jason. - Train A moving 85 miles an hour--
我说生活中的例子
I meant an example from our lives.
我还没说完，我们坐在火车B上
Well, you didn't let me finish. We we're on train B.
去你的，别说笑了
Damn it, be serious.
-你要严肃的例子？ -是的
- You want a serious example? - Yes.
好吧
Okay.
这件事不告诉你是不想让你生气
Here's something I didn't tell you because I thought it might upset you.
我不会生气的
I will not be upset.
几周前我在洗衣店碰见阿里森了
A couple of weeks ago I ran into Alison Van Dyke at the dry cleaners.
-你的旧女朋友？ -是的
- Your old girlfriend? - That's the one.
太好了
How nice.
怎么不告诉我碰见阿里森了？
Now, why wouldn't you want to tell me you ran into Alison?
-不知道，我觉得你会.. -不高兴？
- I don't know, maybe I thought you"d-- - Be upset?
胡说，她现在还卖肉吗？
Nonsense. Does she still strip for money?
麦姬，她是艺术模特
Maggie, she's an artist's model.
那么她去洗衣店干嘛？
And what does she have to dry-clean, anyway?
把自己塞到洗衣机里？
You'd think they could just hose her down once a week.
之所以不告诉你嘛
See, this is exactly why I didn't want to tell you.
我不高兴不是因为你碰见她
Oh, no, I'm not upset that you saw her.
而是因为你隐瞒我
I'm upset that you hid it from me.
你跟那个一丝不挂的说些什么了？
So, what did you and the nudist talk about?
我就是应该隐瞒你
See, I knew I that I should've kept this to myself.
对!隐瞒你那些肮脏的秘密
Right! That and all your other squalid, little secrets.
失陪了，我出去散步
Well, if you'll excuse me. I'm off to do a little jogging, Jason.
看完今晚是不能做第37条了
Well, I guess that means no Number 37 tonight.
累了，饿了，闷了
I'm tired. I'm hungry. I'm bored.
我要去厕所，真讨厌 你也很讨厌
I have to go to the bathroom. I'm sick of this. I'm sick of you.
这就对了，继续说说讨厌什么
That's the spirit! Tell me more. Tell me what you hate.
什么都讨厌，我讨厌这房子.
I hate everything. I hate this house.
讨厌这地毯，这沙发垫，这桌子
I hate this rug, this sofa cushion, this table.
我讨厌他的睡衣
I hate his pajamas.
-他是怎么了？ -他要破牢骚的纪录
- What's with him? - He's going for a record in complaining.
他要发牢骚连续62小时
He has to complain for 62 straight hours.
目前已经连续2分钟了
So far, he's got two straight minutes.
我讨厌分钟，我讨厌手表 我讨厌你的脸
I hate minutes. I hate stopwatches. I hate your face.
我就让你好好讨厌
I'll give you something to complain about.
我讨厌被个子大的人殴打
I hate getting beat up by people bigger than me.
我讨厌疼痛
I hate pain.
本，到楼上寻找讨厌的东西吧
Ben, lets go upstairs and find something for you to hate.
我讨厌楼梯
I hate stairs.
我讨厌这个钟，我讨厌这些蜡烛.
I hate this clock, and I hate these candles and....
麦克，准备好上第一堂课没？
Hi, Mike. Ready for the first class?
林达，不是说在课堂见吗？
Lynda, look, I said I'd meet you down at the karate place.
我知道，但一起走路上学更有趣
Oh, I know. I just thought it'd be more fun if we walked together.
不是吗？我不能来这里？
Was I wrong? It is okay that I'm here, isn't it?
不，我带你参观我家
Yeah. Look, why don't I give you a tour of the house.
这是厅里的壁厨
This is the hall closet here.
-爸爸 -麦克
- Hey, Dad. - Hi, Mike.
你妈妈散步回来没有？
Your mother come back from her jog yet?
还没有
No, not yet.
-还以为听到她声音呢 -不，不是她
- I thought I heard her voice. - No, Dad, that wasn't her.
麦克，空手道的事你还是坦白吧.
Mike, you know, there's no use in you and I discussing this karate thing anymore...
多说无益
unless you're gonna be straight with me.
班上肯定是有女孩子
Now, I still think there's a girl in this class.
不可能
No way, Dad.
好吧，是有这么一个
All right. Well, maybe there is one girl.
但这女孩奇坏无比
But we're talking flea collars and milk bones.
这女孩是头猪
This girl is the Elephant Girl.
西弗先生，幸会
Nice to meet you, Mr. Seaver.
谁说黛比是畜生了？
You thought Debbie DiZomba was an animal.
嗨
Hi.
别管我，我进来找眼镜在不在
Don't let me disturb you. I just think I left my glasses in here somewhere.
在
So you did.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
Don't mention it.
行了，不打扰你了
Well, that's all I wanted. I won't bother you any more.
不打扰
It's no bother.
其实我有一小时空闲时间 若有话要说.
In fact, I have a free hour if there's anything you'd like to discuss...
西弗太太.
Mrs. Seaver.
医生.
Well, Doctor...
我有些烦恼
there is something troubling me.
我知道
I knew it.
我是个心理医生，我有这种触觉
I'm a psychiatrist. I sense these things.
可以说说看吗？
Would you like to sit down and tell me about it?
是我的丈夫
It's my husband.
-他怎样了？ -他行事荒谬
- What about him? - He's impossible.
我很爱他，他是个好父亲 但有时候.
I mean, I love him, and he's a great father, but sometimes--
-他打你了？ -没有
- Does he beat you? - No.
-他酗酒？他在公共场所裸露？
Drink to excess? Scratch himself in public?
没有
No.
那怎么个行事荒谬？
Then why is he so impossible?
他不完全坦白
Because he doesn't believe in total honesty.
西弗太太，你现在完全坦白了吗？
Mrs. Seaver, are you being totally honest with me now?
是的
Yes.
有个确保的方法
Well, there's one sure way to find out.
催眠
Hypnosis.
催眠？
Hypnosis?
盯着这个催眠器
You just keep your eye on the hypnotic trance inducer.
厉害
Very impressive.
可以看看花式表演吗？
Now may I see you do Walk the Dog.
表演要收钱的，西弗太太
Not for these prices, Mrs. Seaver.
你感到很疲惫
Now you're getting tired.
眼睛睁不开了
You can barely keep your eyes open.
你睡着了
You're out.
万试万灵
Works every time.
西弗太太，你现在不能说谎了
So, Mrs. Seaver, you are now incapable of telling a lie.
你说的将会都是真话
And everything you say will be the complete and absolute truth.
-知道吗？ -知道了
- You understand? - Yes, Doctor.
首先简单测试一下
All right. Well start with a simple test question.
你认为丈夫的红色格子亲衫如何？
What do you really think of your husband's red plaid blazer?
他的红色格子亲衫？
His red plaid blazer?
跟他的牙肉颜色.
Well, I think that it really brings out the color of his...
很相称
gums.
全部都要是真话
The whole truth, Mrs. Seaver.
那是除了卡在洗手盘的 那条凯罗的蛇以外.
I think it's the ugliest thing I've seen since Carol's snake...
我所见最恶心的东西
got caught in the dishwasher.
很好，这才像样
Good. Now we're getting somewhere.
加上那条领带.
And that awful tie he wears with it.
简直像活在杂货店里的人
Makes him look like a thrift shop blew up in his face.
我只是问亲衫的事
I only asked about the blazer.
我只是诚实回答
Just being honest.
我很高兴你喜欢这样
Well, I'm glad you're enjoying this.
西弗太太，我还有一个问题
I have one more question for you, Mrs. Seaver.
去年圣诞派对，马蒂是不是.
By any chance, at last year's Christmas party...
追求你了？
did Marty Brandt make a pass at you?
-你怎么知道？ -我怎么知道不重要
- How did you know-- - Well, it doesn't matter how I found out.
他是不是追求你了？
Did he make a pass at you, or not?
是的
Well, yes.
不过没什么，算不上追求
But it was nothing. I wouldn't even call it a pass.
他邀你去南太平洋度假
He asked you to go to Tahiti with him.
周末而已
Just for the weekend.
你怎么不告诉我？
Well, why didn't you tell me?
丈夫不应该知道.
I mean, doesn't a husband have a right to know...
妻子鬼混的事？
when his wife is propositioned?
杰森，我认为没必要说出来
Jason, I didn't think there was any point in mentioning it.
我不想破坏你和马蒂的友谊
I mean, honey, I didn't want to ruin your friendship with Marty.
而且，马蒂当时喝醉了
Besides, Martyd had too much to drink.
-他不知道自己在干什么 -我知道
- He didn't know what he was doing. - I know.
因为他被拒后，蹒跚来找我
Because as soon as you turned him down, he staggered over to me...
含含糊糊都说出来了
and blabbed the whole sordid story.
马蒂告诉你了？
Marty told you?
他坦白了
He confessed.
接着他哭了 还要用我的领带擦鼻子
Then he broke into tears and tried to blow his nose on my tie.
就是称红亲衫那条
The one I wear with my red plaid blazer.
杰森，对不起
Jason, I'm sorry.
我应该告诉你的
I should have told you.
也许吧
Maybe.
也许你认为说出来有百害而无一利
Or maybe you realized that telling me wouldn't do anybody any good...
于是就一言不发
so you kept it to yourself.
我欣赏你这一点
I admire you for that.
是吗？
Really?
若是马蒂没喝醉酒 你早就告诉我了
And I'm sure if Marty had been sober, you would have told me everything.
度假回来就会马上告诉我
As soon as you got back from Tahiti.
若是阿里森没穿衣服 你也会告诉我
And I'm sure you would have told me if Alison had been nude.
度假回来马上告诉你
Right after we got back from Tahiti.
杰森
Jason.
西弗医生，谢谢你
I mean, Dr. Seaver. Thank you.
-你帮了我很大的忙 -是的
- You've been very helpful. - Yes.
这次心理治疗效果显著
Well, it has been a most productive session.
我有事想要试验一下
However, there's one other thing I'd like to try with you.
我从来没对病人试验过的
Something I've never tried before with a patient.
试验什么？
What's that?
第42题
Number 42.
医生
Doctor.
你被催眠的，无法抗拒
There is no use resisting. You're under hypnosis.
谁抗拒了？
Who's resisting?
世界纪录的人收到信后.
When those world record people get this letter...
肯定会让我们入围
well be in that next edition for sure.
你们破了什么纪录？
So, what record did you guys break?
一天内尝试破纪录最多次的纪录
Most failed attempts trying to get into the World Record Book in one day.
这种纪录是不成立的
And they said it couldn't be done.
爸爸，妈妈，我可以学现代舞蹈吗？
Mom, Dad, can I take modern dance?
[zeroxia@gmail.com] 2006.03.12